Gross, James Additional Research Files /4186
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James Gross Additional Research Files
1916-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gross, James
/4186
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8036587
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James Gross NLRB Files /4057 P: James Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4186: James Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James Gross Additional Research Files 5697: James A. Gross Arbitration Files 5959: James Gross Additional Arbitration Files /4079: James Gross Additional Files
Gross, James.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8036587
- General Council Bott Announces Two Personal Changes, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Materials NOT Used reFNS. Ch 8 Footnotes Ch 8 (Folder 1 of 2), 1947-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Materials NOT Used reFNS. Ch 8 Footnotes Ch 8 (Folder 2 of 2), 1947-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NLRB + Arbitration, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Secondary Activity, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Race-Hate Cases, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- GE Coalition Bargain, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Craft Severance Mallinckrodt Chem, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Columbia Law Review Race Post L-6, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Administrative Procedure Act and A Congressional Committee Speaks Out on the National Labor Relations Board, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ch 13 Lab Ct Proposals Bkground there 63, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NAM Meetings + NAM Opposition, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NLR Reports and Other Notes, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vol. 18, 1964 Vanderbilt Law Review "Gould" (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Labor Articles (Folder 1 of 4), 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Labor Articles (Folder 2 of 4), 1961-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Labor Articles (Folder 3 of 4), 1966-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Labor Articles (Folder 4 of 4), 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Post 1968 Election (Box 1, Folder 19)
- National Labor Relations Board Write Up and Memorandum for the Honorable Frank W. McCulloh, 1961-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- National Labor Relations Board Papers + Other articles relating to labor, 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Union Secondary Boycott Activities (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Articles Relating to Labor, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Articles Relating to Labor + Notes, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Articles Relating to Labor and the National Labor Relations Board, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1965 + BRC + Labor Law (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Pre 1968 Election Hill & Knowlton (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Personal Notes + Articles Relating to Labor, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Garment Textiles, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Remedies See also: J.P. Stevens, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Remedies See also: J.P. Stevens (Folder 2 of 2), 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Articles Relating to Labor and the National Labor Relations Board, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Footnotes Used Ch 11, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Articles Relating to Labor + Summaries of National Labor Relations Board Meetings, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Articles and Notes Relating to Labor, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Articles Relating to Labor and Unions, 1956-1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Law Reviews and Letters to The President/ Senator, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Papers Relating to the National Labor Relations Board, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- LPA McGuiness BK 63, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Articles Relating to Labor + Minutes From Meetings, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Labor Law Reform Study Amendments to the Labor Management Relations Act, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Hearings Before the Special Subcommittee on Labor of the Committee on Education and Labor House of Representatives, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Papers Relating to the National Labor Relations Board + Amer. Unions, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Misc Tree NAT Woodwork, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Labor Reports and Articles, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Organizing Class Speech, 1949-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NLRB 1960's BD Budget- Backlogs, Delegating Anth, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 14 B, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Hearings before the Special Subcommittee on Labor of the Committee on Education and Labor House of Representatives- Part I+ II, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Papers Relating to National Labor Relations Board and Unions, 1965-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Darlington, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Darlington + Conclusion File, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Common Situs (Folder 1 of 2), 1950-1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Common Situs (Folder 2 of 2), 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Labor Papers + The White House Press Conference Write Up, 1960-1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Newspaper Articles + NLRB File Index (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  # 68-72 are missing
- Annual Report of the National Labor Relations Board 26- 35, 1961-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- National Labor Relations Board Study + Other Related Papers, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- National Labor Relations Board Papers (Folder 1 of 2), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- National Labor Relations Board Papers (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- National Labor Relations Board Papers and Notes to Prof. Gross, 1970-1988 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Brown Papers, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Letters, National Labor Relations Board Papers, + Partial Transcript of Addresses and Remarks at Conference of Regional Directors, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Labor Importation, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Black Professional Workers and Prof. Assoc., 1942 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Black Organizations, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Reconversion, 1944-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Local Political Influence on FEPC goals, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Organized Labor, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Relations with Federal Agencies as Employers, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Press Relations (general), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Background Info: Statistics, Progress Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Migration, 1940-1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Labor Papers and Gov. Reports, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Gross- Historians and the Literature of the Negro Worker Psnl.c.1, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Gross- Historians and the Literature of the Negro Worker Psnl.c.2, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Gross- Historians and the Literature of the Negro Worker Psnl.c.3, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Gross 406 Bibliography Psnl.C.7 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Gross 406 Bibliography Psnl.C.8 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Journal of Negro History "Letters of Negro Migrants of 1916-1918" Psnl.C.2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Journal of Negro History "Letters of Negro Migrants of 1916-1918" Psnl.C.3 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Journal of American History "article by Salmond" Psnl.C.1, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Journal of American History "article by Salmond" Psnl.C.3, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Journal of American History "article by Salmond", 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Social Forces "article by Ross" Psnl. File C.2, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Social Forces "article by Ross" Psnl. File C.1, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Wisconsin Magazine of History "article by Fishel" Pers. File C.2, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Wisconsin Magazine of History "article by Fishel" Pers. File C. 3, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Wisconsin Magazine of History "article by Fishel", 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Crisis "article by Davis", 1935 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Crisis "article by Peck" Dep. File C.4, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Documents From Files of Division of Negro Economics & Karl Phillips PsnL.C.3, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Black Women, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Development of A Definition of Discrimination, 1944-1946 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Executive Orders Organizational Structure Chronology Also Committee Politics and Members, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Case Cites and Materials, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- FDR and Truman, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Relations with Congress/Lobbying/ Political Support, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Coworker Attitudes + Management, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Relations with Federal Agencies Re: Enforcement, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Permanent FEPC, etc., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Black Press, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Individuals, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Black Veterans (Education), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Jurisdiction and Enforcement: Procedures Remedies, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 42)